Does he know how much grief he's causing everyone?
Isn't what you did unjust, Annie?
How much would he have craved this child?
Be it unjust or cruel,
I can't abandon him.
For him I am just a tool
But ...
I am a mother.
Now, we will have our own children
So?
He was the first life to stir within me.
How can be not be my son?
The mistake is mine,
I did not need this second life.
The price I paid for this?
Das!
Yes Annie, Das is also a husband.
A husband who had the misfortune
of witnessing his own wife bear another man's child.
Self-esteem was sacrificed that day.
My ears from the mockery.
To the locals, do you know who Chandra Das now is?
A man who rented out his wife to another man.
A 'gentleman' who lives off that money.
A reminder of my misfortune,
I won't be able to stand this burden being with us for the rest of our lives.
Then,
you can abandon me Das.
I will carry this burden alone.
After one more year,
you will be able to enter the field again Das.
Become a proud star for the fans.
But Annie and her son will not come there
as a testament to your humilation.
Remain calm Rajeev.
We can find a way.
Yes! Why fear needlessly
Just now I brought you on bail so easily.
And that too considering all the charges.
Intimidation, ???
If it was another advocate,
there would've been an order to put you in remand.
That would've been better.
Life imprisonment with no chance to leave early.
Advocate, will we get the child back?
We must get it.
The case might be complicated.
We can argue with two points.
Firstly, breach of contract.
Acting contrary to the agreement.
Then, cheating.
Betrayal of trust.
Isn't there a legal way of claiming the child?
Isn't that the contract?
This contract's strength is our strength.
We wrote this then only on my insistence!
And if we hadn't?
This advocate Govindan is only called ??? by ???.
No one with brains will do that. What do you say?
That we can say after the case is over.
You too must come to the court.
As a witness.
It is based on this ??? contract, that the
second party is now keeping the child in their custody.
That is a breach of contract under Section 406 of the Indian Contract Act.
Two lakh rupees in cash was received.
Rejecting all terms agreed to verbally and in writing by the other party, is a betrayal of trust.
Cheating.
Section 420 of the IPC.
I humbly request the court to take action
to return the child to my honest client. ???
That's all Your Honour.
Your Honour.
My client does not reject the contract terms mentioned earlier.
But for artifical insemination, and for the actions
taken by the first party, there is no legal standing in India.
And so, ???
this contract is invalid.
It is an illegal contract.
My client is married.
Her husband is still alive.
So, legally possession of this child
is assigned to my client's husband.
Marriage certificate is produced.
So I request Your Honour, to set aside the contract.
That's all Your Honour.
Thank you.
This agreement is against the Indian Contract Act.
So the petition is rejected.
Your Honour,
as a special case?
Sir, everything stated in the petition is true.
I don't know the law.
But he is my son!
You must give him to me!
What you are saying might be true.
But legally there is no possibility.
You can appeal anywhere.
But no court in India will consider this.
What are you thinking?
I was thinking about Rajeev.
When the court said the contract is illegal,
he became very despondent.
God is with me.
Then, God is unjust.
You're still unable to understand me, Das.
I know.
But, I can understand everyone.
You have hatred for my son.
That's why you're speaking for him.
It's not hatred, Annie.
I had desired to share my life with you.
Didn't you just now say my son?
He will always be your son.
He can never be ours.
He will always only be your son.
And I will be alone.
I can't stand that Annie.
Do not think like that.
You will always be with me Das. You must.
Isn't that why I did something that
no other woman would do?
I didn't know that I would come to love this child.
When he grows up, will he not go in search of his father?
No, my son will not leave me.
Else, let him leave if he wants to.
Until then, he is our son.
My Das will be his father.
Will you not love him like a child, Das?
Don't cry Annie.
Don't cry.
You've gone back to your old ways?
Yes.
The restart went beautifully.
No issues.
There's one thing that will make you happy.
Don't you say that these assets will all get taken by others.
Don't need to fear that now.
My son.
This will all be his.
Come, go to bed.
- No.
I was resting all this while.
Enjoyed a dream while sleeping.
Eight to ten months.
That's gone.
In a way, it was good
that it happend like this.
Because ...
he won't be like me.
He'll get everything I didn't.
A good mother.
He'll growing listening to lullabies
and being loved. ???
Couldn't we watch this from afar, Uncle?
Son, why are you getting sad like this?
No, I am not gettng sad.
Oh, the tears right?
That must be tears of joy.
Yes.
Joy.
Mother!
Annie, don't fear.
I have not come to steal him away.
But to ask once more in the name of humanity.
I have only him as a relative.
I have not loved anyone or been loved.
Life was a flow until now.
Flowing somewhere.
Since my son's birth,
a lot of new things,...
... many plans were made
and a new life were just beginning.
All the love I saved until now,
I gave to him.
When all that is being lost,
I can't bear it.
So, can't you take everything that's mine
and give me just my son?
No, I won't give him.
Okay, leave it.
Chandradas ...
I didn't want to spend the rest of my life wondering...
'What if I had asked just one more time?'
That's why I came here today, like a beggar.
I have a request for you Chandradas.
Do not hate my son.
When he grows up ...
.. don't tell him the story of this stupid father.
When he grows up, he'll come looking for you.
It's certain.
Thank you.
Will I be alive then?
May I hold him for a moment?
Give it to him, dear.
All my assets will be for him.
Don't insult me as a money-minded fool.???
I felt very proud to be called a father.
Not once did you call me like that.
Goodbye.
If tomorrow he asks us,
"Didn't you destroy my father?" ...
what will you reply Annie?
Did the doctor, midwives and nurses leave?
They left in the morning itself.
Why didn't you leave Maggie?
Didn't you get all your wages?
Yes.
I wanted to leave after coming and seeing you.
I know you are very sad, sir.
No.
Who said?
After a marriage, more children can be born.
I don't want that.
I had the crazy thought of having a son.
That's over.
Are there any other crazy thoughts?
Give me a glass.
Now in this home, alcohol and smoking are allowed, right?
Haven't you heard the tale of the mouse-maid who turned back into a mouse?
What is it Chandradas?
Your child.
Annie?
No one could compete with the love you showed him.
Did Annie agree?
She had to agree.
Take him.
Maggie.
- Sir
This is not a dream, right?
- No
If I didn't do this, then I would never have peace
in the new life I owe to your generosity.
Thank you.
Annie is in the car.
We are leaving this place.
She needs a change.
Otherwise...
What is this Annie?
Hadn't you agreed to everything?
I can't. I can't leave him.
Leave me.
Give me my son back. I need him.
I need my son.
Annie!
So you don't want me?
Tell me.
You have to decide between the two.
If you have even a little love for me,
then you must come with me now.
Otherwise, don't expect Chandradas later.
Take him.
Annie's son.
You may go.
Chandradas.
You are a great man.
Else you wouldn't have shown me this much pity.
Don't trap her in a competition.
Maybe you would lose.
That must not happen.
Enter.
We might not come back.
Be happy wherever you are.
I have a final request.
Don't refuse it.
Amidst all the changes, I developed some unnecessary beliefs.
If I die, please allow him to do ??? and whatever may be the final rites.
That is the tradition.
It is the son who should light the father's funeral pyre.
As you would know Chandradas.
At least in the afterlife, let me find peace.
Annie.
I have only happiness.
My son will grow well.
I am beginning to learn a lot through you.
You may leave.
Are all mothers like Annie?
Yes my child.
I know what's in your mind.
Were you not thinking about your mother?
I have also heard.
That woman will never have been happy.
Her whole life she would've been in pain.
In the same way that Annie loves her son...
can you love me Maggie?